reachoutrecovery.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy - Reach Out Recovery

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy applies only to information Reach Out Recovery collects at and through the Site.  Our Site also contains links to third party sites that are not owned or controlled by Reach Out Recovery.  Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information.

Terms of Use.  Please note that your use of our Site is also subject to our Terms of Use.

INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT

Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide to us, for example when you request information from us, contact customer support, or otherwise communicate with us. This information may include your name, email address and telephone number.

Information We Collect Automatically Through Your Use of our Site

We and our service providers use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Site through your computer or mobile device. A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the Site again, the cookie allows the Site to recognize your browser. Cookies may store unique identifiers, user preferences and other information. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Site features or services may not function properly without cookies. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences and tracking user trends.

No Information from Children Under Age 13

If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to register with us at this Site or provide any personal information about yourself to us.  If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete that information.

HOW WE USE AND SHARE YOUR INFORMATION

To Provide Products, Services, and Information.  We collect information from you in order to provide information that you request from us.

Sharing with Third Parties.  We may provide information to third party service providers that help us operate and manage our Site. These service providers will only have access to your personal information if it is needed to provide these services, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service.

Legal Proceedings.  We will share personal information with third party companies, organizations or individuals outside of Reach Out Recovery if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to:

  * Meet any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, legal process or enforceable governmental request.
  * Enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations.
  * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of ARC, our users, customers or the public as required or permitted by law.

Transfer in the Event of Change of Control.  If the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes or we otherwise transfer assets relating to our business or the Site to a third party, such as by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy proceeding or otherwise, we may transfer or sell your personal information to the new owner. In such a case, unless permitted otherwise by applicable law, your information would remain subject to the promises made in the applicable privacy policy unless you agree differently.

ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION AND CHOICES

If you have questions about personal information we have about you or need to update your information, you can Contact Us at Reachoutrecoverymedia.com

SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use industry standard physical, technical and administrative security measures and safeguards to protect the confidentiality and security of your personal information.  However, since the Internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot guarantee, ensure, or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.  There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  It is your responsibility to protect the security of your login information.  Please note that emails and other communications you send to us through our Site are not encrypted, and we strongly advise you not to communicate any confidential information through these means.

CONSENT TO PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA IN UNITED STATES

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) or other jurisdiction outside of the U.S., in order to provide our Site, products and services to you, we may send and store your personal information (also commonly referred to as personal data) outside of the EEA, including to the United States. Accordingly, your personal information may be transferred outside of the country where you reside or are located, including to countries that may not or do not provide the same level of protection for your personal information.  We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of personal information when it is transferred. Where such transfers occur, we take appropriate steps to provide the same level of protection for the processing carried out in any such countries as within the EEA to the extent feasible under applicable law. By using and accessing our Site, users who reside or are located in countries outside of the United States agree and consent to the transfer to and processing of personal information on servers located outside of the country where they reside, and that the protection of such information may be different than required under the laws of their residence or location.

CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your consent in accordance with applicable law. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of privacy policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

QUESTIONS AND HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions, concerns, complaints or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy or otherwise need to contact us, please email us  call us at 941 366 0870, or contact us by US postal mail at the following address:

1800 2nd Street Suite 870 Sarasota, FL 34236
